casinowiz.com 2015-02-09

# Privacy Policy | Your Online Casino Review Guide

## Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
We hereby guarantee your privacy. Thus, in order to better protect it, we wish to inform you about our practices regarding gathering and storing your information, along with the list of options you have if you wish to change the way in which your information is used on our site. This page is always reachable by clicking on the Privacy Policy link, found on the footer of every page on our website.  
What information we collect  
This privacy policy you are reading is applicable to all information submitted to or collected by Casino Wiz.  
Some of the webpages on our site might require you to have an account in order to access them. By creating one you are prompted to provide the following information

  * Name
  * Email Address  
Location
  * Country
  * Some of the webpages will allow you to forward our articles via email, simply by entering the recipient’s information:
  * Name
  * Email Address

In both of the cases mentioned above, we hereby guarantee that the information collected will not be sold, distributed or traded in any way. Promotional newsletters will be delivered to members, but only if they have opted-in to receiving them.

**How we use the collected information**  
The information you submit to us will only be used to maintain a brief profile about who you are, and will never be shared with outside parties, unless deemed necessary by law.  
Your e-mail address will be used by us in order to deliver you our promotional offers and newsletters, marketing material, latest bonuses available at top tier casinos, daily/weekly/monthly promotions, etc., but only if you have opted-in for this feature.  
Other information we collect and store on your computer may include cookies and session data that will identify you as a user, if you wish to remain logged into your Casino Wiz account. This information will not, under any circumstances, compromise your identity, because not only do cookies not store personally identifiable data, but they are also secure as to not make it visible to anyone who might have access to your computer.

**We guarantee data security**  
In order to prevent any potential unauthorized access, we have special protocols and procedures implemented so as to avoid any data theft or security breaches.

**Privacy of minors**  
Anyone under the age of 18 is not allowed to create an account with Casino Wiz. All our members must meet our minimum age requirement in order to benefit from our services.

**Contact us at any time!**  
Should you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please refer to our FAQ’s page or e-mail us at info@casinowiz.com.
